Guide to the George F. Kunz Papers 1862-1932 MS 358
New-York Historical Society
- Silskey, Edward (New York Public Library), 1894, 1909, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  1894 letter, on Columbia College Library stationery, is in German.
- Sinclair, R.R. (Harper & Brothers), 1891 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Skiff, Fredrick J.D., 1903, 1909, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Universal Exposition, 1904; Field Museum of Natural History
- Skinner, Charles M. (Brooklyn Daily Eagle), 1893 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Skinner, John, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Sleicher, John A. (Leslie's Weekly), 1911-1916 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Sloan, Robert S. (Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission), 1909 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Sloane, William, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Sloane, William Milligan, 1906, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  An exchange of letters primarily from 1917 concerning New-York Historical Society. Sloane, of Columbia University, is a member and on a committee to consider the work and scope of N-YHS. He solicits suggestions from Kunz, who offers two concerning annual meetings and banquets intended to make the Society more public, useful, and likely to attract funding.
- Smith, Acheson (Union League), 1931 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Anna Walton, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Benjamin E. (Century Co), 1900, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Courtland (American Press Association), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, David Eugene, 1924-1932, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Edgar F. (University of Pennsylvania), 1914, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Edward (Columbia U. Library), 1916 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, E.E. (National Magazine), 1916 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, George Otis (U.S. Geological Survey), 1906 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Smith, Isabelle Dwight Sprague, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  One letter concerns a George Montgomery Tuttle Memorial Fund Committee. and a second letter (to Mrs. Kunz) concerns a circular for a school.
- Smith, R. Hobart, 1890, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Soeding, Emil, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Solch, Joseph M. (New-Yorker Staats-Beitung), 1906 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Southard, George F., 1921, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Southwick, Albert A., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Sprague, Frank J. (Museums of the Peaceful Arts), 1925 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Spencer, Alexander H., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Spencer, J. Beaumont (National Security League), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Spice, Robert (Cooper Union), 1916 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Springer, Frank, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stanton, Ella O'Gorman, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stanton, Gilman S. (Stanton Brothers, manufacturers), 1918 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Star, E.G., 1903 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Starr, Frederick (University of Chicago), 1905 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stedman, Arthur, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stedman, Edmund C., 1903 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stedman, Laura, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stedston, C.A. (J.B. Lippincott Co), 1928 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Stephens, Annie W. (National Shakespeare Federation), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stetson, Clarence (New York Herald), 1891 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stevens, Horace J. (Peninsular News Bureau), 1908 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stevens, Mary S., undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stevens, W. LeCoute (Packer Collegiate Institute), 1886 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stewart, Albert S., 1918 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stewart, Edith Adams, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Includes note about lecture, program of lecture, "Series of Four Lecture-Readings on Continental Contemporary Drama at the Hotel Majestic (72nd Street) and news article on same.
- Stewart, John A. (Sulgrave Institution), 1920-1925 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stewart, William J., 1913, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stillman, James A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Includes a copy of the pension plan put in place by The National City Bank
- Stimson, Margaret, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stitt, Edward W., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stokes, I.N.Phelps, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stokes, James, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stone, Isabelle, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Stone writes at length about her time as a physics professor at Vassar, her inability to advance to head of the Physics Department, her resignation from Vassar, and her career/professional prospects and search as a woman in the field at that time.
- Stone, Melville E. (Associated Press), 1915, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stowe, Lyman Beecher (Doubleday Page & Co), 1922 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stoudt, John Baer (Huguenot-Walloon New Netherland Commission), 1924 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Strachey, J.S.Loe (The Spectator), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Stratton, S.W., 1925 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Straubenmuller, Gustave (School Garden Association of New York), 1926 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Street, George A., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Stripley, A.R. (Christ's College), 1906 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Includes short biography on William - 4th Earl of Fitzwilliam.
- Strong, Benjamin, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Struthers, Joseph (American Institute of Mining Engineers), 1908 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Sturgis, Lyman B. (Century Co), 1930 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Sturgis, Russell, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Sullivan, George M. (Cathedral of St. John the Divine, Layman's Club), 1915-1921 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Sunday, William A. (Billy Sunday), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  The letter informs Kunz that Sunday is sending a string of crystal beads to be fixed. Includes a sheet from a serial, The Fra, (pp. 185-186) about Billy Sunday.
- Swart, Mary (City History Club), 1924-1930 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Documents, including a progam, for the club's 34th Annual Entertainment, chaired by Kunz and held at the American Museum of Natural History.
- Swope, Herbert Bayard (The World), 1917 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Symthe, Jr., J.Henry (National Republican Club), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Misc. S, 1893-1932 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Tack, Augustus Vincent (Century Association), 1919 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Takamine, Jokichi, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Tanner, Virginia (American Pageant Association), 1921 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Taw Sein Ko / Toʻ Cinʻ Khui (Archaeological Survey, Burma), 1910 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Typed article on Burmese Necromancy with hand-drawn figures.
- Taylor, Frederic (Taylor & Walsh, financial brokers), 1885 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Teall, Gardner C. (2 folders), 1896-1924, undated (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
- Terry, Jr., John T., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thatcher, John Boyd, 1893, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thayer, [first name?], 1928 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thayer, Stephen Henry (Authors Club), 1912-1918 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thomas, John Lloyd, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thomas, Theodore (Century Association), 1916 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thompson, Robert M. (Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission), 1909 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thompson, Vance (or Laura?), undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thompson, W.C. (Columbia U., "The Dorms"), 1909 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thomson, Elihu, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thorndike, Ashley H., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thurston, Ada, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Thruston, Gates P. (Tennessee Historical Society), 1907 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Tihanyi, Paul P., 1916 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Tiffany, Louis C. and Katerina Ely Tiffany, 1901, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  2 letters from Louis, one from Katerina. In the 1901 letter, Louis responds to Kunz saying that the "signs for fountain" (?) are being made but going slow. In an undated letter, Louis thanks Kunz for specimen sent and for berry branches. In an undated (circa 1901) letter, Katerina thanks Mrs. Kunz for the bracelet and telegram of congratulations.
- Tillinghast, C.B. (State Library of Massachusetts), 1897 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Tod, J.Kennedy, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Toedteberg, Emma (Long Island Historical Society/Hudson-Fulton Celebration), 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tolman, William H., 1900, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tombo, Lorraine, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tombo, Jr., Rudolf, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Torrey, Lillie Gay, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Toscanini, Walter (bookseller), 1929 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tower, Ralph W. (American Museum of Natural History), 1913 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Towne, Henry R., 1904, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Townsend, R.D. (The Outlook), 1908 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Trask, Katrina, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Treadwell, H.H. (Tiffany & Co), 1911 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  One announcement of a Tiffany stockholders meeting.
- Treadwell, Villa Gray, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Treman, Robert H., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Trent, W.P., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Includes a copy of Trent's poem "Austria-Hungary: 1914-1915.", by W.P. Trent
- Trout, S. Edgar, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Trowbridge, M.E.D. (Mrs. L.H.), 1908 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Trumble, Alfred (The Collector), 1892, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tucker, John F. (Twilight Club), 1918 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tuckerman, Eliot (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Turle, Kathleen G., 1913 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Turner, Homer G. (Lehigh U), 1925 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Tyler, Viola, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Updike, Berkeley, 1926, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vail, Charles D. (Hobart College), 1908-1909 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vail, Theodore (Museums of the Peaceful Arts), 1913 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Valentine, Herbert (American Numismatic and Archaeological Society), 1899 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Two documents concerning specifications for two volumes regarding a General Grant Monument Medal.
- Van Amringe, J.H. (Columbia College), 1906-1907 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Van Anda, C.V., 1920 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Van Anda, Louise D. (City History Club), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Van Brunt, Jeremiah R. (Union League), 1929 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vance, Arthur T. (Woman's Home Companion), 1902 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vanderbilt, Cornelius and Cornelius Vanderbilt, Jr., 1915, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  One Vanderbilt letter to Kunz and one from Kunz regarding the Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet. One letter of introduction for Frederick Hamill from Vanderbilt Jr.
- Vanderlip, Frank A. and Narcissa Cox Vanderlip, 1914-1919 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Among other documents, Kunz writes briefly to Mr. Vanderlip (President of the City National Bank of New York) in response to Vanderlip's article on food shortages, and Vanderlip writes about his position on the adverse impact on business of the war (World War I). Mrs. Vanderlip requests financial assistance to establish at Lake Mohegan a unit of the Woman's Land Army.
- Van Dusen, Elizabeth (Mrs. Samuel C.), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Van Hise, Charles R. (University of Wisconsin), 1906 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Veazie, Henry Pursell (Cathedral of St. John the Divine), 1925 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  One letter in which Veazie briefly explains his resignation as Precentor of the Cathedral.
- Verplanck, William E. (Century Association), 1904-1906 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vickers, George E., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Offer of barium from his mine in Maryland for exhibit at the St. Louis Exposition
- Villard, Fanny Garrison, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vincent, George E. (Museums of the Peaceful Arts), 1925 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vizitelly, Frank H. (Funk & Wagnalls), 1912, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Voynich, Wilfred M., 1918 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Vrooman, John W., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Includes a short biographical sketch of John Wright Vrooman
- Wade, Blanche Elizabeth, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Includes a St. Patrick's Day rhyme written by Wade.
- Walcott, Charles D. (Carnegie Institution; Smithsonian), 1904, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Walker, E.D. (Harper & Brothers), 1886-1887 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Walker, John Brisben (Cosmopolitan Magazine), 1891-1893, 1903, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Walker, William Bogart (Christ Church, Herkimer, NY), 1884 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wall, Alexander J. (New-York Historical Society), 1924, 1928, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wallace, Celia W., 1894 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wallace, Charles William, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  One letter with an extensive description by Wallace of his financial needs for continuing his (unspecified) research.
- Wallin, William J., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Walters, H. (Century Association), 1899 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wannamaker, Rodman, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Ward, Herbert D. (The Independent), 1885 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Ward, J.H. (Bethlehem Steel, for Charles M. Schwab), 1919 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Ward, Lydia Avery Coonley, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Includes a program for Summer School for Children at the Free Library, Wyoming, New York
- Ward, William Hayes (The Independent), 1891-1908, 1919, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wardwell, Allen (Legal Aid Society), 1929 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Warfield, Edwin, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Waring, Vechten, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Warner, F. (British Museum), 1901 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Warner, Worchester Reed, 1929, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Waterman, Frank D., 1925 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Watson, Albert C., 1890 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Watson, Archibald R. (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Watson, Mark S. (The Sun), 1930 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Webster, William King, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Includes several flyers explaining the TIPI Order of America, Original American Indian Order Founded by Indians -- William King Webster is the Acting Great Tally Chief. Letter from Webster to Kunz indicates Kunz was a member.
- Weekes, Gladys O., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Weinman, Adolph Alexander (Century Association), 1921 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Welcher, Manfred P. (Anti-Cigarette League of America), 1912 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Weld, Jr., De Witt C., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Weldon, M.L. (New York Times), 1923 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Welling, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Wells, Charles H. (Piedmont Exposition; "The Dixie"), 1887-1888 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Wells, T. Tileston, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Letter from president of the Alliance Francaise de New York informing Kunz of his election to membership.
- Wellstood, Frederick C. (Trustees & Guardians of Shakespeare's Birthplace), 1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- William Wesley & Son (booksellers), 1884-1890 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Westervelt, Leonidas, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Whalen, Grover A. (Mayor's Committee of Welcome to Home-Coming Troops), 1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wheeler, Amy L. (Needle and Bobbin Club), 1921 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Letter informing Kunz of his acceptance as club member.
- Wheeler, Edward J. (Current Opinion), 1916 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wherry, Edgar (U.S. Department of Agriculture), 1918 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whidden, Bradlee (bookseller), 1886 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- White, Andrew D. (Museums of the Peaceful Arts), 1913 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- White, W.A., 1917 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whitfield, E.A., 1907 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whitehouse, Vira Boarman, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whiting, F. Allen (Handicraft magazine), 1911 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whiting, Gertrude (Needle and Bobbin Club), 1921 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whitlock, Herbert P. (New York State Museum), 1917-1918 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Whitney, Evelyn J., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wickersham, George W., 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  American Society of the French Legion of Honor; National Probation Association
- Wilcox, Ella M., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wilder, Eric (Laymen's Club), 1929 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wile, Ira S. (Civic Club), 1916 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wiley, Harvey W. (Good Housekeeping), 1913, 1928-1929 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- John Wiley & Sons (publishers), 1903 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wiley, Louis (New York Times), 1923-1931 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williams, Arthur, 1915-1916, 1927, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet; American Museum of Safety
- Williams, Daniel (Century Association), 1905 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williams, H.B., undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williams, Robert Leslie (International Who's Who), 1909 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williams, Stephen G., 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williams, Talbot, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Williamson, E.D. (New York Evening Post), 1924-1925 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilmot, F.M. (Carnegie Hero Fund Commission), 1917 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, Christine Towne, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, F.T. (Youth's Companion), 1884 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, James Grant, 1903, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, L.B., 1909, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, Theodore (The Pilgrims club), 1919 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Wilson, W.P. (Commercial Museum, Philadelphia), 1924 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Letter from Museum Director Wilson describes the collection in response to Kunz's question of removing it to New York.
- Winchell, Edward Everett (printer), 1894 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Winecoff, Thomas E. (Rev), undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Incomplete letter
- Wingate, George Albert (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Winship, George S. (Harvard U. Library), 1924 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wirts, Walderman, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wise, Joseph H., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Witherbee, Frank S., 1912 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wittpenn, Caroline B., 1920 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wolbarst, Abraham L., 1915 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wood, H.T., 1891 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Woodford, Stewart L., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Woodhouse, Henry, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Includes as part of Christmas letter - A copy of letter from Byrd Antarctic Expedition, Letter re Aerial League of America, and invitation to visit Washington D.C.'s new Thousand Acres Airport
- Woodman, Edward, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Woods, William Seaver (Literary Digest), 1921, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Woodward, R.S. (Carnegie Institution), 1907, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wright, Orville, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  One carbon copy of a letter to Wright regarding the possibility of an industrial museum in New York and proposing to acquire Wright's "machine" for it.
- Wright, Richardson (Authors Club), 1918-1919 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Two letters, one of which is Wright's proposal to Kunz that Gardner Teall be nominated to membership.
- Wright, Thomas T., undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wright, W. Aldio (Trinity College, Cambridge), 1892 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Wucher, Father (St. Vincent de Paul's Rectory), 1928 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Request for contribution for memorial to the French of New York who died in World War I. In French.
- Misc. W, 1887-1925 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Grolier Club; Century Association; others.
- Yardley, Margaret, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Young, (James?) Carlton, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Young, M.I. (Mrs. William H.), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Zerban, F.H., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Tells Kunz of his support for introducing the metric system.
- Illegible Correspondent Signatures, 1893-1917 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Dinner/Luncheon Menus, 1896-1930 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Dinner given to Professor Henry Moissan (with various autographs); dinner in honor of European Members of Transcontinental Excursion of 1912 (with various autographs); dinner of the Hunters Fraternity of America to Monsieur Maurice Maeterlinck (1920); Society of Chemical Industry banquet (1928); luncheon tendered to the officers, passengers and crew of the Graf Zeppelin by the Advertising Club of New York [1928]; dinner in honor of D. Bryson Delavan (1930), with Kunz's notes on Edward Partridge who sat at Kunz's table but later fell ill and died; one card with autographs (undated).
- Acknowledgements from Libraries of Books Received from Kunz, 1899-1912 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Invitations, 1887-1890, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Several meeting invitations from Grolier Club; one ticket to loan exhibition at Aldine Club; invitation to celebration of 250th anniversary of founding of Kingston, NY (1908).
- Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Forms soliciting patrons and patronesses for the Committee on the Entertainment of Naval Officers and the Foreign Guests; publicity letters sent to organizations; draft of description of College of the City of New York exhibition.
- Receipts & Statements, 1888-1925 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Dues receipts for Grolier Club (1888) and American Folk-Lore Society (1893); transmittal of check to Kunz for articles for Saturday Evening Post (1908); invoice for medals in connection with Authors Club Walt Whitman Memorial Committee (1925).
- Poem, 1862 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Manuscript poem "Line." "Written on our troops crossing the Potomac, March, 1862." Unsigned.